http://www.mercuryluggage.com/pages/privacy-policy-1

PRIVACY POLICY
We at Advantus Corporation, including Advantus-owned companies, brands, and websites (referred to as “Advantus,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of certain information collected about our customers and prospective customers (referred to as “Customers,” “you” or “your”). This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. At Advantus it is our intention to give you an understanding about how we collect your information and the use we make of it in the course of our business. To that end, Advantus gathers two types of information about Customers: data that Customers provide through optional, voluntary registration on our sites, use of our services, or purchase of our products, including your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, and, if required to complete a purchase or if you voluntarily add it to your account, your payment/billing information (“”Personal Information”); and data Advantus gathers through aggregated tracking, mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites (“De-Identified Data” or “Aggregated Data”). Such information enables us to tailor our content to fit Customers’ needs better and to help our advertisers understand our audience. However, be assured that Advantus will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as may be noted in this Privacy Policy.
How does Advantus collect information?
Site registration, service request, or product purchase: We collect information by specifically requesting it from you. Generally this occurs when you register at a site or request information or a service. Usually, the Advantus sites and Advantus’s service partners use your information to operate the sites and to deliver services. Advantus sites also use your information to inform you about other products or services available from Advantus and its affiliates. If you make a purchase from one of our sites, then we collect Personal Information to meet our obligation to fulfill your order(s).
Provision of this Personal Information is mandatory in some instances, for example, you need to provide an email address to create a user account and you need to provide several categories of Personal Information to allow Advantus to fulfill an order.
Usage tracking
Use of Internet Protocol (“IP”) Addresses: An IP address is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Internet so that your computer can be identified by the main computers, known as “Web servers,” that “serve up” Web pages. Advantus and/or its affiliates collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to audit the use of our site. When Customers request pages from Advantus’s and/or its affiliates’ sites, our servers log the Customers’ IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a Customer’s session will be logged, but the Customer will remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a Customer when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site terms of use or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others.
Use Of Cookies: What are cookies? Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site sends to yours computer for record-keeping purposes, which information is stored in a file on your computer. Cookies make Web surfing easier for you by saving your preferences so that we can use the saved information to facilitate your use of our Web site when you return to the site. Cookies do not tell us your individual identity unless you have chosen to provide it to us. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and as such, you’ll find that most major Web sites use them.
By showing how and when Customers use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our Customers’ needs.
Most cookies expire after a defined period of time, or you can delete your cookie file at any time. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of Advantus and/or its affiliates’ services will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized preferences, and/or may have difficulty completing marketing transactions.
Advantus and/or its affiliates primarily use cookies to track Customers’ Web site usage trends and patterns. This helps us understand our Customers’ needs better and improve areas of Advantus’s and/or its affiliate’s services that our Customers find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of cookies, you have the option of disabling the cookies via your browser preferences.
With whom does Advantus share my information?
As a general rule Advantus will not disclose any specific Personal Information that you submit to us about you in a manner that connects you with the Personal Information, except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your Personal Information may be disclosed.
Aggregated Data: Advantus may keep track of what portions of the Web site Customers are visiting and other Customer statistics, and aggregate this information to help us create a better experience for users of our Web site. This is all done without Advantus knowing your name or other Personal Information in order to describe our viewers and services to prospective partners and for other lawful purposes.
Other: Advantus may also disclose Personal Information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Advantus’s terms of use or terms of service, or may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with any of Advantus’s rights or property, other Advantus Customers, or anyone else. Advantus may disclose or access Personal Information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.
How can you control the usage of information?
We give you the opportunity to control the communications we direct to you. We offer Customers the opportunity to “opt in” to having Personal Information shared with Advantus and/or its affiliated companies. At any time, you may object to the processing of your information, on legitimate grounds, except if otherwise permitted by law. You can also contact Advantus to:
Request access to information that Advantus may have about you
Correct any information that Advantus may have about you
Request that Advantus change, restrict, or object to the way we use information we may have about you
Request that Advantus delete information we may have about you and/or provide you a copy of such information
If you have any additional questions about Advantus’s collection and storage of data, please contact us at info@advantus.com or 904.482.0091.
What happens when you link to a third party site?
You should be aware that when you are on Advantus’s and/or its affiliates’ sites you could hyperlink or be directed to other sites that are beyond our control and/or outside our service. For example, if you “click” on a banner advertisement or an Advantus.com search result, the “click” may transfer you off the advantus.com site. These other sites may include sites of advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use Advantus’s and/or its affiliates’ logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to Customers, collect data, or solicit Information.
Advantus and its affiliates do not control such sites, and, therefore, are not responsible for their contents or the hyperlinks or advertising they choose to place on such sites. Advantus’s and/or its affiliates’ inclusion of hyperlinks to these sites do not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites or any association with their operators. Advantus’s policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, which is beyond Advantus’s and its affiliates’ control. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out information online (for example, via message boards or chat) that information can be collected and used by people you don’t know. While Advantus and its affiliates strive to protect their Customers’ information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you disclose such information at your own risk.
Is my Information secure from others using the Advantus site?
The importance of security of all information associated with our Customers is an important concern to us. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, Advantus and its affiliates can’t ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, Advantus uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.
All orders on our site are encrypted using 128 bit Secure Socket Layer Technology (SSL). SSL is an extremely complex form of cryptography that makes it virtually impossible for a third party to decrypt any personal information you provide. Your personal and credit card information is securely protected when transmitted online. You can use any search engine to learn about SSL and how it works. You can start learning by visiting http://webopedia.com/TERM/S/SSL.html.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS
By using this site, you signify your agreement to Advantus’s Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE. Your continued use of Advantus’s and/or its affiliates’ sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
To request a copy of your data, to request deletion, or if you have any questions or complaints concerning our privacy practices, please contact us via email at dataprivacy@advantus.com or fill out our request form via this link.
©Advantus Corp. 2019. All rights reserved.
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection
